buzzamin.com 2016-04-18

# Privacy Policy – Buzzamin

****Your privacy is important to Buzzamin.com. This privacy statement provides information about the personal information Buzzamin.com collects, and the ways in which Buzzamin.com uses that personal information.

**Personal Information Collection  
**The types of personal information Buzzamin.com collects are:

  * Information about your use of this website
  * Demographic and interests reporting

**Securing your Data  
**Buzzamin.com will take reasonable technical and organizational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information. Buzzamin.com will store all the information you provide (on its secure servers). [Information relating to electronic transfers entered into via this website will be protected via encrypted technology.]

**Using Cookies  
**We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information.

**Consent  
**By using our site, you consent to our website’s privacy policy.

**Updating this Statement  
**Buzzamin.com may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on this website. You should check the page periodically to ensure you are familiar with any changes.

**Other Websites  
**This website contains links to other websites. Buzzamin.com is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third party.

**Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance  
**We do not provide services directed to children or otherwise target our site to children, and we do not collect personal information from children under the age of 13. No content that depicts, describes, identifies or otherwise relates to an individual under the age of 13 may be submitted to us, and no such content or other information relating to an individual under the age of 13 will be knowingly solicited or received by us.

**Contact  
**If there are any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, or if you wish to change or delete any information previously provided by you or collected from you, you may contact us at [support@buzzamin.com](mailto:support@buzzamin.com).
